A Guide to the Documents from the County Manager's Library, 1889-1994
Arlington Public Library, Center for Local History
- BOX 97
  - Arlington County Budget, 1967-1968
  - Arlington County Budget, FY 1971 1970-1971
  - Arlington County Budget, FY 1972 1971-1972
  - Arlington County Budget, FY 1973 1972-1973
  - Arlington County Budget, FY 1974 1973-1974
  - Arlington County Budget, FY 1975 1974-1975
  - Arlington County Budget, FY 1976 1975-1976
  - Arlington County Budget, FY 1977 1976-1977
- BOX 98
  - Arlington County Budget, FY 1978 1977-1978
  - Fiscal 1978 Proposed Budget, Volume 1: Activity Decision Packages
  - Fiscal 1978 Proposed Budget, Volume 2: Budget Detail
  - Fiscal 1979 Proposed Budget, Volume 1: Activity Decision Packages, Capital Improvement Program
  - Fiscal 1979 Proposed Budget, Volume 2: Budget Detail
  - Fiscal 1979 Adopted Budget
  - Fiscal 1980 Proposed Budget, Volume 1: Activity Decision Packages
  - Fiscal 1980 Proposed Budget, Volume 2: Budget Detail
  - Fiscal 1980 Adopted Budget
  - Fiscal 1981 Proposed Budget, Volume 1: Activity Summaries
  - Fiscal 1981 Adopted Budget
  - Fiscal 1982 Proposed Budget
  - Fiscal 1982 Adopted Budget
  - Fiscal 1984 Adopted Budget
- BOX 99
  - Fiscal 1985 Proposed Budget
  - Fiscal 1985 Adopted Budget
  - Fiscal 1986 Proposed Budget
  - Fiscal 1986 Adopted Budget
  - Fiscal 1987 Proposed Budget
  - Fiscal 1987 Adopted Budget
  - Fiscal 1988 Proposed Budget
  - Fiscal 1988 Adopted Budget
  - Fiscal 1989 Proposed Budget
- BOX 100
  - Fiscal 1989 Adopted Budget
  - Fiscal 1990 Proposed Budget
  - Fiscal 1990 Adopted Budget